translated by "S"
트로이입니다
메세지 남겨주세요
This is Troy. Leave a message.
집에 있어?
전화 좀 받아
Are you home? Pick up.
배고픈데
뭐라도 주문해야겠어
I need food.
I want to order something.
과카몰리가 먹고 싶어
I am craving guacamole.
이제 차 세운다
I'm puling up.
여보세요?
Hello?
집에 도착했군, 케이트
I see you made it home, Kate.
제발 내버려 두세요
Please leave me alone.
죄송해요
Sorry.
안돼, 안돼!
No! No! No!
안돼!
No! No! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
제발, 누가 좀!
Please, somebody! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Aah! Ohh!
안돼!
No! No!
살려주세요!!
Somebody, help me!
Aah!
Stalker 1x01
Pilot
Original Air Date on October 1, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
해마다 6백만 명 이상의 미국인이
스토킹을 당하고 있습니다
Over 6 million people are
stalked each year in the United States.
여성 6명 중 하나,
남성 19명 중 하나 꼴이죠
1 in 6 women, 1 in 19 men.
스토킹은 타인에 대해
원치 않는 관심과 집착을 쏟는 것입니다
Stalking is the unwanted or obsessive
attention from one person to another.
거부, 질투, 복수심에 의해
유발되기도 하죠
It's driven by rejection,
jealousy, revenge.
Hi.
가방 들어 줄게, 알았지?
I'll take your bag, all right?
일찍 데리러 갈거야
I'm gonna get you early, OK?
좋아요
언제쯤이요?
OK. How early?
스토킹은 잘못된 관계의
결과로 비롯되거나
Stalking can be the result
of a relationship gone wrong
극단적인 망상장애로
인해 생길 수도 있습니다
or delusional fixations
that are pushed to extremes.
누구든 스토커가
될 수 있어요
Anyone can be a stalker...
옛 애인, 배우자
낯선 사람이요
Ex-boyfriend, spouse, stranger.
누구나 피해자가 될 수도 있고
최근 그 수가 중입니다
Anyone can be a victim,
and it's on the rise.
페이스북, 트위터,
인스타그램, 스냅챗, 틴더 등
Facebook, Twitter,
Instagram, Snapchat, Tinder,
최근 유명한
어떤 앱을 통해서든지
whatever app is hot today,
우리는 서로에게 과도한
접근을 하게 됩니다
we have too much access
to one another.
SNS가 최근 수십 년간
Social media is
the number one reason
스토킹 사건을 세 배로
증가시킨 주된 이유입니다
stalking cases have
tripled in the last decade.
그래서 제가 있는 거죠
That's where I come in.
저는 LA 경찰국의
스토킹 전담 수사팀인 TAU를 맡고 있고
I run TAU, the threat
assessment unit of the LAPD
정치가 및 일반인들에 대한
스토킹이나 위협을 조사합니다
we are responsible for all stalking
cases and threats to individuals,
as well as politicians
and city employees.
어떤 상황이든 그 위협의 수준을
평가하고 대처하는 게 저희 임무입니다
It is our job to assess the level of threat
in any situation and respond accordingly.
제 얘기 듣고 계신가요?
좀 지루해하는것 같네요
Have I lost you?
I'm seeing eyes glaze over.
이건 어떨까요?
궁금한 점 물어보실래요?
How about this?
Any questions for me?
'셀레나 고메즈'의
스토커도 잡으셨나요?
Did you handle
the Selena Gomez stalker?
'데이비드 레터맨'의 집에
수십 년간 침입한 스토커가 있었대요
I heard David Letterman
had a stalker for over a decade,
some lady who kept breaking into his house.
전자는 제가 안 잡았고
후자는 맞습니다
No, I didn't,
and, yes, he did,
유명인에 대한 스토킹은
전체의 10%밖에 되지 않아요
but celebrity stalking makes up
only 10% of all stalking cases.
대부분의 피해자는
우리 같은 일반인이죠
Most victims are like you and me.
오셨네요
Good morning. The lab work came
back on the mayor's bloody cake.
시장님의 피로 범벅된 케이크
조사 결과가 나왔어요
메이플 시럽이 들어간
식용 색소였죠
It was red food dye
mixed with maple syrup.
말씀대로 장난이었어요
You were right.
It was a prank.
시장 집무실에 연락했어?
Call the mayor's office?
네, 시장님이
얘기하고 싶대요
Yes, and the mayor
wants to talk to you.
순 겁쟁이야
내가 전화하지
He scares so easy.
I'll call him.
어제 버뱅크에서
있었던 총격 사건이요
Homicide has more on
yesterday's Burbank shooter.
일용직 노동자를 겨냥한
시(市) 공무원으로 밝혀졌어요
Turns out it was a city employee
targeting street workers.
준비됐는데,
제가 조사할까요?
I'm up.
Can I do the assessment?
제니스랑 같이 해
You can share
it with Janice.
내가 뭐랬어
I told you.
제니스, 뭐 좀 알아봐 줄래?
Janice, can you do
background for me?
알코트 대에 다니는
남자애 두 명인데
Two boys at
Alcott University--
에릭 베이츠,
페리 위틀리야
Eric Bates,
Perry Whitley.
좋은 아침이에요
새 사건인가요?
Good morning.
Is this a new case?
'딘'이 부탁한 건데
나중에 만나러 가야 해
It's a favor to the Dean.
I have to see her later.
라슨 형사님 오셨어요
Detective Larsen is here.
누구?
Who?
새로 발령받은
라슨 형사님 말이에요
Detective Larsen,
transfer, the new guy.
지금 회의실에
모셔 놨어요
I put him
in the conference room for now.
일찍 왔군
He's early.
안녕하세요
전 베스 데이비스 경위예요
Hi. I'm Lieutenant Beth Davis.
LA에 잘 오셨어요
Welcome to L.A.
안녕하세요?
잭 라슨 형사입니다
How you doing?
Detective Jack Larsen.
반갑군요
Nice to meet you.
아는 거 있어?
What do you know about him?
뉴욕 강력계에서 왔고
From New York, Homicide,
13번째 부서 이동에
엄청난 개성의 소유자야
13th precinct, big personality,
not for everyone.
결혼한 적 없는 독신에
바람둥이래
Single, never married,
sleeps around.
잘됐네
Good for him.
- 상관의 부인과 잤어
- 오, 그래서 쫓겨났군
- Slept with some high-up's wife.
- Oh, and he got the boot.
확실히 구제불능이지
Apparently he can't help himself.
경위님이 싫어할 걸
Beth is gonna hate him.
뉴욕에서 9년간
강력계에 있었네요
9 years NYPD Homicide.
성과도 좋았고요
Good record, decorated.
왜 여기로 왔죠?
Why the stalkers unit?
'스칼렛 요한슨'을
만나고 싶어서요
Well, I was hoping to
meet Scarlett Johansson.
분야가 전혀 달라요
It's an entirely different skill set.
우리 목표는
범죄 예방이에요
Our goal is to prevent crime,
관련된 사건과
관리해야 할 것들도 많고
so there's a lot of
case management involved.
정신 질환에 과한
배경지식이 필수적이죠
A background in mental
illness is necessary.
메뉴얼 읽었나요?
Have you read the manual?
아뇨, 하지만
'위험한 정사(1987)'는 봤죠
No, but I watched "Fatal Attraction,"
'옵세스(2009)'
'마이 보드가드(1980)'
"Obsessed," "My Bodyguard,"
"Cape Fear," "Swimfan."
'케이프 피어(1992)'
'위험한 유혹(2002)'도요
네, 읽었어요
Yes, I read the manual.
그냥 농담한 거예요,
정신병에 대해서도 잘 알고
That was... that was a joke, and
I'm well versed in mental illness,
정신분열증, 자기도취증,
양극성 장애(조울증)
everything from schizophrenia,
narcissism, bipolar disorder,
저도 해당되는
망상 장애까지!
delusional psychosis... My own!
방금 것도 농담입니다
Another joke.
알아요, 잘 압니다
I get it.
I totally get it.
스토킹과 위협을 일삼는
미치광이들을 잡는 일이죠
It's a very specific whack job
that stalks and makes threats.
왜 여기서
일하고 싶은 건가요?
Again, why do you want to be in this unit?
이미 이 팀인데요
I'm already in this unit.
서류도 작성했고
수속도 다 마쳤어요
I filled out the paperwork,
my transfer was processed.
- 틀렸나요?
- 맞아요
- Am I wrong?
- No.
왠지 면접을 보는
기분이 드네요
Because this was starting
to feel like an interview.
현재 우리 팀에는
6명이 있어요
There are currently 6
Detectives in the unit.
각자 자기가 맡은
사건을 책임지고 있지만
Each Detective is responsible
for his own caseload,
작은 팀이기 때문에
다 함께 일하죠
but we're a small unit,
so we work together.
한 달 동안 하는 거 봐서
좀 풀어주도록 하죠
You'll tale me for a month,
and then I'll turn you loose.
제가...
잘못 말 한 게 있나요?
Did I, uh--did I
say something wrong?
무슨 뜻이죠?
What do you mean?
뭔가 굉장히 나쁜
첫인상을 준 느낌이라서요
I'm getting a vibe like I just
made a really bad first impression.
'스칼렛 요한슨' 얘기는...
I know the Scarlett
Johansson comment was...
- 느낌이요?
- 그래요
- A vibe?
- Yeah.
날 싫어하는 것 같아요
Like you don't like me.
바보 같은 소리 마요
내가 이따금씩 무례하게 굴어요
Don't be silly.
I'm sporadically rude.
살인 사건이 터졌어요
Homicide dumped a murder on us.
반가워요
전 제니스 로렌스예요
Hi. I'm Janice Lawrence.
넥타이 멋지네요
Nice tie.
어젯밤 살해를 당했어요
Woman was murdered last night.
케이트 에드워즈,
28살에 독신입니다
Kate Edwards--
single, 28,
산 채로 불에 탔죠
burned alive in her car.
벤 콜드웰이에요
반갑습니다
Ben Caldwell.
Nice to meet you.
이전의 사건 파일은?
Any prior case files?
희생자가 7월에
불법 침입 신고를 했어요
The victim reported
an intruder in July
10월에는 공공 기물
파손으로 또 신고했고요
and again in October, a
vandalism report a year prior.
할리우드 스테이션에 있는
경찰서에 여러 번 갔었는데
She went to the police several
times, Hollywood station,
스토킹으로
분류되지 않았어요
but it was never
classified as stalking,
그래서 우리한테
오지 못한 거죠
so never made its way to us.
좋아
가보죠, 신입
All right.
Let's go, new guy.
첫 번째 출동이에요
Time for your first assessment.
당국은 폭발로 숨진
케이트 에드워즈 사건의
Authorities are
searching for a suspect
in the murder of a
young woman Kate Edwards,
용의자를 찾고 있습니다
who was burned alive
in a fiery explosion.
스토킹 수사 전담반이
사건을 맡았다고 알려진 가운데
Sources tell us
the threat assessment unit
of the L.A. police
department has been called in
수사에 관해 밝혀진
내용은 아직 없습니다
to supervise the case, and no
other details have been released
regarding the ongoing investigation.
거의 다 됐습니다
We're almost done.
여기에서 오래 살았는데
생활감이 거의 없어요
She hasn't been here very long.
The place is barely lived in.
우편물들도
우편집중국에서 받고
Her mail goes to a mail center.
누군가에게서
숨어 지냈네요
She's been hiding from someone.
겁에 질렸으니까요
Because she was terrified.
어째서죠?
How so?
욕실에 투명한
샤워 커튼이 있는데
In the bathroom, she has
a clear shower curtain
아무도 숨을 수
없게 하려고 한 거죠
so no one can hide behind it,
침대 밑에 숨을 수 없게
바닥과 가까운 침대를 썼고요
a platform bed
close to the ground
so no one can hide under it.
오랫동안 안정감을
갖지 못했어요
She didn't feel safe,
hadn't in a long time.
이 방을 좀 봐요
Look at this room.
풍수(風水)도 전혀
고려하지 않았어요
For an interior designer,
it's not feng shui at all.
침대는 방 문을 바라보게
이쪽 벽에 있어야 하죠
The bed should be on this
wall facing the door, no,
근데 여기에 있다는 건...
but it's over here because...
침대 왼편에서
잠을 잤군요
She sleeps
on the left side of the bed.
잡동사니가 있는
테이블을 봐요
Note the cluttered
side table on her side
현관을 향한 거야,
그림자를 조심하려고
facing the door...
to watch for a shadow,
문 아래로 스토커의
발걸음을 볼 수 있게요
the footsteps of her stalker
to appear under the door.
수면 장애가 있지만
약을 먹길 거부했겠죠
She had trouble sleeping but
refused to take sleeping pills.
약장에 일 년 치
처방전으로 가득하더군요
There's a full prescription from a
year ago inside the medicine cabinet.
너무 무서워서
잠도 잘 수 없었어요
She was too afraid to sleep.
- 그럼 스토커는?
- 남자죠, 현실을 직시해요
And her stalker?
It's a man.
Let's face it.
산 채로 불에 태우는 짓은
남자들이 한다고 나와 있어요
The violence of burning
someone alive
has us men written all over it.
역할 놀이를
즐기는 놈이에요
He likes role-playing.
판타지를
실현 시키려고
He wants his fantasy,
so he breaks
그녀가 없을 때
침입했어요
into her apartment
while she's gone,
그녀의 침대에서 자고,
그녀의 음식을 먹고
sleeps in her bed,
eats her food,
그녀의 TV를 보며
파고들어 갔죠
watches her TV,
lives in her world.
눈치챌 수 있을 만큼만
흔적을 남겼을 거예요
He would leave little clues
so she would know he was here
아니면...
미치게 하려고 했거나
or... just to make her crazy.
뭐가 부추긴 걸까요?
What set him off?
당신이 묘사한 놈은
성적으로 집착하고 있었어요
The predator you described
suffers from eroto-fixation.
이 여흥을 즐겼으니
끝내고 싶지 않았을 걸요
He likes the journey. He
doesn't want it to end.
왜 죽였을까요?
Why kill her?
아직 몰라요
I don't know yet,
하지만 나 때문에
감명받았죠?
but I impressed
you a little bit, didn't I?
'트로이 건'이라는
사이좋은 이웃이 있대요
There's a neighbor--
Troy Gunn.
They were good friends.
집에 있어?
전화 좀 받아
Are you home? Pick up.
배고픈데
뭐라도 주문해야겠어
I need food.
I want to order something.
과카몰리가 먹고 싶어
I am craving guacamole.
이제 차 세운다
I'm puling up.
밤새 집에 있었어요
I was here all night.
전화기를
무음으로 해 놨었죠
I had my phone on silent.
친하셨나요?
You two were close?
작년에 꽤
가까워졌어요
Yeah. Real close for the past year.
그 스토킹 때문에
친해지게 된 거예요
This whole stalking mess
brought us closer.
실내 자전거반에서
처음 만났죠
We met in a spin class at the gym.
지난번 살던 곳에서
괴롭힘을 당했다더군요
She told me she was being
harassed at the last place.
제가 옆집이
비었다고 말해 줘서
I told her that--when
next door became available.
이사를 왔어요
She moved in.
두 분이
교제하셨나요?
Were you two ever involved?
그냥 친구였어요
No. We were just friends.
그 이상을 원했군요
But you wanted more.
아니요,
친구 사이입니다
No. We were just friends.
이 아파트의 모든 집에서
'할리우드 사인'이 보이나요?
Do all the apartments have
a view of the Hollywood sign?
북쪽 집들만요
On the north side.
배우이신가요?
You an actor?
부동산 중개인입니다
I'm a realtor.
하지만 배우가 되려고
LA에 오셨죠
But you came to L.A.
to be an actor.
10년 전에는 그랬지만
지금은 부동산 업자예요
Yeah. 10 years ago,
but I'm a realtor now.
케이트가 사귀던
사람이 있었나요?
Was Kate involved with anyone?
일 년쯤 전에 은행가인
래리 마이어스와 만났어요
The last guy was over a year
ago, a banker Larry Myers.
오래가진 못했죠
Didn't last long.
알고 보니 유부남이라
케이트가 찼어요
Turns out he was married.
She found out.
She dumped him.
화장실 좀 써도 될까요?
Could I use your bathroom?
옆집은 범죄 현장이라
소변을 못 봤어요
I can't pee next door.
It's a quasi crime scene.
그러면 참으세요
Then you're gonna
have to go hold it.
내 물건 뒤질
생각하지 마시고요
You're not gonna snoop
through my stuff.
난 스토커가 아닙니다
I'm not Kate's stalker.
참아요, 잭
Yes. Hold it, Jack.
케이트가 래리를
의심한적 있었나요?
Did Kate ever
suspect Larry Myers?
처음에 그녀가
솔직하게 물었어요
At first.
She asked him point blank.
그는 아니라고 했고요
He denied it.
잘못해서 고소하고
싶어하지 않았죠
She didn't want to
falsely accuse him.
아이가 있는
유부남이었거든요
He was married with kids.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
래리?
Larry?
형사님들이 찾아왔어요
Two detectives are here.
케이트 일은
유감입니다
Sorry to hear about Kate.
어젯밤 어디 계셨죠?
Mr. Myers,
where were you last night?
아내와 같이 있었어요
Here all night with my wife.
마지막으로
케이트를 보신 건요?
When's the last time
you saw Kate?
일 년 전에 저한테 와서
선물과 메모를 보냈냐고 물었어요
A year ago.
She came to me and asked
if I'd been sending her
these notes and gifts.
전 아니었지만 그녀는
스토킹을 당한다고 생각해서
I wasn't, but she thought
she was being stalked
이사를 할
생각이라고 하더군요
and was thinking about
moving because of it.
의심 가는 사람을
얘기하지 않았나요?
She never mentioned anyone
she suspected?
제가 한 짓이라고
의심했어요
No. She suspected me.
She thought I was doing it,
내가 목이라도
맨 것처럼요
like I was hung up on her.
그랬나요?
Were you?
제가 못할 짓은 했지만
스토킹을 할 사람은 아니에요
I made a mistake with Kate,
but I'm not the stalker type.
보시다시피
전 결혼을 했어요
You know, I'm a married man.
어젯밤 알리바이를
부인이 확인해 주실까요?
Can your wife confirm
your alibi last night?
네, 하지만
케이트 일은 몰라요
Yes, she can, but she
doesn't know about Kate.
왜 바람을 피웠나요?
Why'd you have an affair?
초라한 중년 남자가
하는 짓이 이렇죠
I'm a miserable middle-aged man.
It's what we do.
부인이 뒷받쳐 주는데
사실일까요?
His wife backed him up.
Is she telling the truth?
글쎄요
I don't know.
그거 언제 풀어
헤치려나 했어요
I was wondering
when that was coming off.
데려다 줄게요,
난 약속이 있어요
I'm gonna take you back.
I have one more appointment.
가슴 쳐다본 거
사과할게요
I'm sorry I stared at your breasts.
뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
그래서 나를
싫어하는 거잖아요
That's why you don't like me.
처음 만났을 때
당신 가슴 훔쳐봤어요
When we first met,
I-I looked at your breasts.
진심이에요?
Seriously?
짐작이 가는 건
그게 다예요
That's all I could come up with.
I was pleasant and personable,
난 유쾌하고 매력적인 데다
지적인 면도 적절히 보여 줬어요
I showed a reasonable
amount of intelligence,
잘생겼고
자존감도 높아요
I'm good-looking,
I have a healthy ego.
내가 한 잘못은
The only wrong move I made was
당신 상반신을
약간 오래 훑어봐서
when my eyes lingered
in your upper torso area
순간적으로 나를
싫어하게 만든 거예요
for a second too long it triggered
an instant dislike for me.
어떻게 하면 될까요?
How do I fix that?
왜 그랬어요?
Why did you do it?
속옷이 비치는 실크 블라우스에
붉은 메니큐어를 발랐잖아요
You're wearing a silk blouse, hint
of a bra, red fingernail Polish.
주목받고 싶어하는 줄 알고
기뻐하길 바라면서 쳐다 본 거예요
I took the male leap that
it was meant to be noticed
and let my eyes linger
in hopes that you
would be flattered.
근데 내가 틀렸죠
I miscalculated.
더 기분 나쁘네요
And it just got worse.
학교의 학생 웹사이트에
이게 올려져 있었어요
This was uploaded on the
university's student web site.
친숙한 영상이지?
You familiar with this video?
네, 봤어요
안본 사람이 있을까요?
Yeah. I've seen it. Who hasn't?
제가 찍지도 않았고
올리지도 않았어요
But I didn't film it, and
I didn't post it online.
이런 질문에 또
대답해야 하는 건가요?
Do I have to answer
these questions again?
저 퇴원해도 된대서
학교로 돌아가고 싶은데요
I've been discharged.
I'd like to get to class.
잠깐만, 페리
내 부탁으로 오신 거야
Please, Perry. Detective
Davis is here as a favor to me.
빨리 끝낼게
We'll be quick.
영상에 나오는
에릭 베이츠 말로는
Guy in the video... Eric Bates...
둘이 룸메이트였던 일 년 전
네가 컴퓨터로 찍은 거라던데
He says you filmed this on
your laptop over a year ago
when you two were roommates.
아니예요,
그 자식이 그냥
No. No. He's just claiming that
자기 체면 살리려고
지어낸 얘기예요
because it's the best story he
can come up with to save his ass.
친구들한테 섹스 비디오를 보여줘서
인터넷에 퍼진 걸 인정하기 싫어서요
He doesn't want
to admit that he showed
his little sex tape to all his buddies
and then they shared it with the Internet.
신입생때 같이 살다가
You lived together freshman year,
2학기가 돼서
에릭이 나간건 왜지?
and then he moved out in
the second semester. Why?
모르겠어요
그냥 이상해졌어요
I don't know. He got weird.
신입생 스트레스에
파티도 엄청 다녔죠
Freshman stress, was partying a lot.
감정 기복이
너무 심했어요
His mood swings were insane.
고소할 생각은 없지만
걔는 열 좀 식혀야 해요
I'm not gonna press charges,
OK, but guy needs to chill out.
왜 고소를 안해?
Why won't you press charges?
누구나 실수는 하니까요
Everybody makes mistakes.
에릭이 문제는 좀 있지만
착한 녀석이에요
Eric has problems,
but he's a good guy.
기회를 한 번 더
주고 싶어요
I want to give him a second chance.
거짓말이에요
He's lying.
병적인 거짓말쟁이라고요
The guy's a pathological liar.
거칠게 대하지
말았어야 한다는 거 알아요
I know I shouldn't have roughed him up.
그 이상이지
You did more than that.
뇌진탕으로 입원까지
하게 만들었으니까
You put him in the
hospital with a concussion.
그 점은 미안하지만
같이 살 때부터 문제였어요
And I'm sorry about that, but
the guy's been trouble ever since
I was roommates with him.
페리는 네가 직접 찍어서
친구들한테 보여줬다고 하던데
He claims that you
made the video yourself
and showed it to your friends.
그 자식이 컴퓨터를 켜 놓고
저랑 크리스티를 녹화한 거였어요
He left his laptop on and
recorded me and Christie.
전 절대로
찍지 않았어요
I would never film a sex tape.
같이 살다가
왜 나간 거야?
You were roommates
with him freshman year.
Why'd you move out?
견딜 수 없어서요
It got too much.
처음엔 좀 샌님 같아도
괜찮아 보였어요
At first, he was cool, a little nerdy.
집안도 좋았고요
He comes from a good family.
Then stuff started happening,
그러다가
이상해지기 시작했죠
증명하기 힘든
자잘한 것들이었죠
little things that you can't prove.
설명할 수 없는데
그냥 이상해졌어요
Just got weird. I can't explain it.
작은 거짓말들을
하는걸 보고
You'd catch him in a small lie,
친구들의 메시지를
전해주지 않거나 하는 것들?
he wouldn't give you messages from
your friends, things like that?
맞아요
Yeah.
둘 다 게이도 아니고
성적인 저의 또한 없어요
Neither boy is gay, there
are no sexual undertones here.
드문 경우 아닌가요?
Isn't that unusual?
스토킹은 로맨틱한 집착
그 이상의 문제예요
Well, there's more to stalking
than just romantic obsession.
페리는 에릭에게 집착하는데
영웅 숭배나 우상화 같은 거죠
Perry's fixated on Eric,
hero worship, idolization.
하지만 페리가
피해자예요
But Perry's the victim.
폭행은 그렇지만
나머지를 속이고 있어요
Of the attack, but he's
lying about the rest.
페리가 어린 시절
부모나 형제를 잃었나요?
Did Perry lose a parent or
a sibling at a young age?
4살 때 어머니가
돌아가셨는데
His mother when he was 4.
그걸 어떻게 알았죠?
How did you know that?
페리는 상실과 거부를
통해서 안정을 느끼겠죠
Well, loss and rejection
become his comfort zone.
이전 룸메이트가 자신을
거부하면 또 찾아 나서고요
His ex-roommate rejects
him, and so he seeks it out.
에릭이 페리의 행동에 관해
얘기했던 게 걸리네요
I'm more concerned about what
Eric said about Perry's behavior.
That's campus police jurisdiction.
그건 캠퍼스 관할권이라
요청 없이는 나도 개입 못해요
I can't intervene
unless you invite me in.
I appreciate the assessment,
사정 조사 와줘서 고맙지만
현재로선 내부적으로 처리할게요
but we're gonna keep this
in house for the moment.
Perry's family are important alumni.
페리 가족이
주요 동문 인사라서요
You'll call me if something occurs.
혹시 문제가 생기면
연락 주세요
물론이죠
도와줘서 고마워요
Of course.
Thanks for the help, Beth.
This day needs to end.
- 오늘은 그만해야겠어
- 그러게 말이야
Tell me about it.
Oh!
Thank you.
고마워요
Bye, Lori.
See you tomorrow.
잘 가, 로리
내일 봐
See you. Bye.
그래, 잘 가
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Help me! Help me!
도와 주세요!
살려 줘요!
Help me! Help me!
도와 줘요! 제발!
What happened?
Hi. Yeah. Yeah.
여보세요, 네
Tell Beth I can meet her.
베스한테
간다고 전해 줘요
I'll be right there.
지금 바로 가죠
Lori Carter,
30, works in finance downtown.
로리 카터, 30살
재무 담당 일을 해요
She was attacked in a parking garage.
주차장에서
공격을 받았어요
First responders handled the report.
최초 담당 경찰들이
보고서를 작성했어요
Is she OK?
상태는요?
Her eyes suffered
some burns, but she's OK.
눈이 좀 데였지만
괜찮아요
She's gonna be released today.
오늘 퇴원할 거고요
Good morning.
좋은 아침이네요
He's been harassing me
for over a year now...
몇 년 동안이나
저를 괴롭히고 있어요
Letters, gifts.
편지에 선물들...
I thought it was harmless.
해로울 것 없다고
생각했었죠
Why didn't you call the police?
왜 경찰에
알리지 않으셨죠?
I know the law.
You can't prosecute
겁준 걸로 기소할 수
없다는 건 저도 알거든요
someone for scaring you.
He didn't hurt or threaten me.
저를 해치거나
위협한 적 없었어요
Do you know Kate Edwards?
케이트 에드워즈를
아시나요?
잘은 모르고 제 아파트의
전 입주자였어요
Yeah. Not well. She lived
in my apartment before me.
I took over her lease.
제가 이어서
세 들어 살거든요
How do you know her?
어떻게 알게 됐죠?
Through my spin instructor Kurt.
실내 자전거 강사인
커트를 통해서요
We went to the same gym.
같은 헬스장을 다녔어요
And Troy Gunn?
트로이 건은 아세요?
There was a Troy
who was friends with Kate.
케이트 친구 중에
트로이라고 있었어요
We're going to need access to your home.
집을 한번 살펴봐야
할 것 같습니다
OK, but why?
좋아요, 근데 왜요?
You haven't heard about Kate?
케이트 소식
못 들으셨나요?
I work 80 hours a week.
주당 80시간을 일해요
She's not a close friend. What?
친한 친구도 아닌데,
뭐죠?
She was murdered two nights ago.
이틀 전 밤
살해당했습니다
Burned alive.
산 채로 불에 탔죠
Stay on this corridor.
혼자 두지 말고
여기 계속 지켜봐
I don't want her alone tonight.
I've seen transference in stalking before,
전에도 스토킹이
옮겨 가는 건 봤지만
but I've never encountered
one man who was stalking
동시에 두 명을
스토킹하는 건 본적 없어요
two women at the same time.
Dual psychosis maybe?
이중인격 일까요?
Well, they lived in the same apartment,
둘 다 같은 아파트에 살았고
운동하는 곳도 같아요
they went to the same gym.
How about you go to the gym,
헬스장에 가서
다른 회원들도 알아 보고
see who else is a member there,
talk to that spin instructor.
강사랑 얘기해봐요
I'll meet you at Lori's. We
need to find this guy fast.
로리의 집에서 만나죠,
놈을 빨리 찾아야 해요
자, 여러분
쉬지 마세요
Come on, you guys. Don't rest.
Here we go! Let's go!
같이 달리죠,
갑시다!
Do a little harder,
and cool down!
조금만 더 달려요,
이제 천천히!
Yeah. I feel great. You feel good?
기분 좋네요,
여러분도 그런가요?
Great job, guys. Great job.
모두 다 잘 하셨어요
최고의 반이네요
Great class. Great class.
I heard about Kate. Sucks.
소식은 들었어요
비극이죠
She took my class all the time
이사 가기 전까지
제 수업을 들었거든요
until she moved into her new place.
And Lori Carter.
로리 카터도요
Yeah. I know her, too. She spins.
네, 로리도 알아요
수업을 들었죠
I haven't seen her much lately.
최근에는 못 봤어요
She moved into Kate's old apartment.
케이트가 살던
곳으로 이사했어요
Which you told her about?
당신이 소개했죠?
Yep. I knew Kate needed someone
케이트가 남은 계약을
채워 줄 사람을 찾았거든요
to take over the lease.
Out of curiosity, Kurt,
궁금해서 그러는데
'와일드'가 진짜 성인가요?
is wild your real last name?
The truth, I did a little softcore
LA에 처음 왔을 때
가벼운 포르노를 찍었어요
when I first moved out here.
It's all over the net.
인터넷에 다 퍼져서
배우 경력은 끝나 버렸죠
Killed any chance of an acting career,
but the name stuck, so I kept it. Heh.
하지만 이름은 남았으니
유지하고 있는 거예요
Where you last night at 10 pm.
어젯밤 10시에
어디 계셨습니까?
Seriously? I had a spin class at 8:00,
진심이세요?
8시에 수업을 했고
did some chest, a shower, and a steam
가슴 운동 후에
씻고 사우나를 했죠
and was out of here right around 10:00.
그리고 10시쯤
여기서 나갔어요
You know Larry Myers?
래리 마이어스를 아십니까?
Yes. He takes my class, or he did.
네, 수업을 듣는데
안 나온 지 좀 됐어요
I haven't seen him in a while.
He was friends with Kate.
케이트의 친구였는데
I don't know how close they were,
얼마나 가까운지는
트로이한테 물어보세요
but you should ask Troy.
- He would know.
- Troy Gunn?
- 그 사람은 알 걸요
- 트로이 건이요?
Yeah. Yeah. He's right over there.
네, 바로 저기 있네요
Mr. Gunn, how are you?
트로이, 반갑네요
Detective, what are you doing here?
형사님은 여기
어쩐 일이세요?
Oh, I'm new to town.
Just checking out the gym.
여기 온 지 얼마 안돼서
운동할만한 곳을 보려고요
What is this, some kind
of grieving workout?
애도하는 마음으로
운동이라도 하십니까?
What are you implying?
무슨 뜻입니까?
로리 카터 아세요?
You know Lori Carter?
Yeah, I do.
네, 알죠
She was attacked
공격을 받았어요
just like your friend Kate Edwards.
당신 친구
케이트처럼 말이죠
Masked man, gas, matches.
마스크를 쓰고
연료에 성냥까지
Where were you last night?
어젯밤 어디 있었소?
Home all by myself,
혼자 집에 있었어요
and, no, I can't prove it.
그리고 증명을
못하겠네요
Cool building. I should
have looked in this area.
좋네요, 이 동네도
둘러봤어야 하는 건데
What's the rent for a place like this?
이런 집은 월세가
얼마나 합니까?
I don't know.
글쎄요
Guess who I ran into at the gym...
헬스장에서 누굴 만났게요?
Kate's neighbor Troy Gunn.
트로이 건을 봤어요
He knows Lori Carter, too,
그가 로리도 알더군요
and he has no alibi for last night either.
간밤의 알리바이도 없고요
"The red dress you wore
last Tuesday was hot.
'지난주 화요일에 입은
붉은 드레스가 정말 멋지더군'
I like your new haircut.
It really gets me going."
'새로 자른 머리도 멋져,
나를 달아오르게 해'
How could Lori not call the cops
그런 걸 읽고 어떻게
경찰한테 신고하겠어요?
after reading something like that?
로리는 강하고 야심적인
전문직 여성이에요
Lori is a strong, ambitious professional.
Being a victim is a sign of weakness,
피해자는 곧
연약함의 상징이니
so she chose to ignore her fears.
공포를 무시하기로
선택한 거죠
It's very human to dismiss a stalker,
스토커를 묵살하는 건
인간적인 반응이죠
or worse... accept it as a part
아니면 생활의 일부로
받아들이던가요
of your daily life.
What?
왜요?
Nothing.
아니에요
What?
뭐예요?
Get up.
일어나요
What is it?
그게 뭐죠?
It's a crawlspace.
공간이 있네요
What is it? What are we looking at?
뭐가 보이나요?
I'm betting we got prints, DNA,
지문에 DNA, 온갖
끈적한 것들을 건졌어요
and lots of other sticky stuff.
It's a secret viewing room.
비밀 상영관이네요
So our freak would just
lay up there and watch her.
이 해괴한 놈이
위에 누워 여자를 본 거요
Above her as if he was on top of her.
마치 여자 위에
눕듯이 있었어요
AFIS has a match
for a background check.
지문 감식 시스템(AFIS)에
일치하는 게 나왔어요
The prints belong
to a banker.
어떤 은행가네요
Let me guess--
Larry Myers.
내가 맞춰 보죠,
'래리 마이어스'
How'd you get in here?
여기 어떻게 왔어?
The R.A. Let me in.
기숙 사감이
들여보내줬어
I explained what happened
무슨 일이었나 설명해주고
화해의 선물을 가져왔어
and came with a peace offering.
I see you have a room to yourself now.
이제 보니 혼자서
방을 쓰는구나
Good for you.
잘됐네
You need to leave.
그만 돌아가
I really want to work this out, Eric.
나 정말 잘 풀고 싶어
Come on. 4 stitches,
cracked rib, concussion.
제발, 네 바늘이나 꿰매고
갈비뼈에 금이 가고 뇌진탕이었어
You can listen.
들어줄 수는 있잖아
OK. I'm listening.
그래, 말해봐
Well, first, I just want
to say I forgive you.
먼저 너를 용서한다는
말부터 하고 싶어
I'm not gonna press charges.
고소하지 않을 거야
You lost your temper. I understand.
순간 화가 나서
그랬다는 거 이해해
And?
그리고?
That's it.
그게 다야
No revenge kick,
no payback?
복수나 앙갚음을
하지 않겠다고?
Payback?
앙갚음?
You make me sound like I'm
some vengeful little bitch.
내가 무슨 복수심에 불타는
계집년인 것처럼 말하네
I just want us to be
friends again like before.
그냥 전처럼
친구가 되고 싶을 뿐이야
Well, we can't be, Perry,
not anymore.
그건 안돼, 페리
더 이상은 못해
How about we just
mind our business
그냥 각자 일이나 신경 쓰고
서로 내버려 두는 게 어때?
and leave each other alone?
Fair enough.
공평하네
Heh. You're... You're funny.
근데 참...
너 웃긴다
Payback.
복수라
You make me sound psychotic.
나를 미친놈으로
만드는구나
I mean, if I really wanted revenge,
정말 내가 복수를
하려고 했다면
I would have poisoned
your beer or something.
맥주에 독약을
탔을 거야
I'm not out to get you, Eric.
널 괴롭히려는 게 아니야
I'm just disappointed is all.
그냥 실망한 게 다지
I didn't kill Kate Edwards.
케이트를 죽이지 않았어요
We found fingerprints and semen
예전 아파트 천장에서
당신의 지문과 정액을 찾았어요
in the ceiling's crawlspace
of Kate's old apartment.
I believe the semen
has yet to identified.
정액은 분석 중일 테고,
공간에 관한 건요?
Regarding the crawlspace, Larry?
Kate used it for storage.
케이트가 창고로 썼었죠
I helped her move some boxes up there
예전에 상자를
옮기는 걸 도와줬으니
over a year ago.
My fingerprints could easily be there.
내 지문도
쉽게 발견된 거겠죠
My client admits
to an affair a year ago
내 의뢰인이 케이트 에드워즈와
불륜을 저지른 점은 맞지만
with Kate Edwards, but he
doesn't even know Lori Carter,
로리 카터는
누군지 모릅니다
and it doesn't matter.
두 건 다 알리바이가 있으니
어차피 상관없죠
He has alibis for both crimes.
What about the 87 hours of footage
압수한 컴퓨터에서 찾은
87시간짜리 영상은요?
we confiscated off your laptop?
What will we find on that?
뭘 찾게 될까요?
I'll have that
thrown out, and you know it.
어차피 채택도
안될 증거물입니다
Charge my client or let him go.
기소하던가
아니면 보내 줘요
We need to talk to his wife.
부인과 얘기를
해봐야겠군
The only way to charge
him is disprove his alibis.
기소하려면 알리바이를
반증하는 수밖에 없소
She's got to be lying for him.
분명 거짓말로
덮어주고 있는 거겠지
Agreed. Did we find
anything on the footage yet?
맞아요, 영상에서
뭐 좀 찾았어요?
I'll check.
확인해보죠
There's someone here for you, Beth.
누가 찾아왔어요
Anything?
건졌어요?
It's a lot of footage,
mainly just Kate sleeping.
대부분은 그냥
케이트가 자는 모습이네요
Larry was definitely
stalking Kate Edwards,
래리가 분명히
스토킹을 한건 맞는데
but there's nothing
on Lori Carter yet.
로리 카터 쪽은
아직이에요
Sometimes he hid his
camera on the bookshelf.
가끔 카메라를
책장에 숨겼어요
Gave him a view of the bathroom.
욕실을 보려고요
What happened?
무슨 일이지?
It's Perry. He's nuts.
페리 때문에요,
그 새끼 미쳤어요
He came to see me
tonight to make nice
오늘 화해하자고
찾아와서는
and then threatened in
that way he does everything.
늘 하던 대로
절 협박하더군요
He can get in my room
whenever he wants.
자기 마음대로
제 방에 찾아와요
Wait. The campus police can't help you?
캠퍼스 경비대는
도울 수 없대?
I've been to them.
찾아 갔었어요
All they know is I kicked his ass.
그저 제가 그놈을
때렸다는 것만 알아요
You know who the guy is.
어떤 놈인지 알잖아요
He's Perry Whitley of the Whitleys.
위틀리 가문의 자식이라고요
They're not gonna do anything.
아무 해결도
못해줄 거예요
I thought you could help.
도와주실 줄 알았어요
Eric, your situation is tricky.
상황이 어려워
I did background on Perry,
페리의 뒷조사를 했는데
너무 깨끗해서
and he's clean, which makes this
so much harder to prove.
증명하기가
훨씬 더 어려워
The first step would be
to get a restraining order,
먼저 접근 금지 명령을
받아내야 하는데
but I can't do that until
I have concrete proof.
그러려면 확실한
증거가 있어야 해
No one gets it. My girlfriend
dropped out of college
못할 거예요
내 여자 친구는 중퇴하고
나랑 말도 안해요
and won't talk to me
because she thinks
I make amateur porn.
내가 섹스 동영상을
찍었다고 믿으니까요
My grades have gone
from a 3.0 to failing
성적도 떨어졌어요
because I can't eat or sleep
날 소유물로 여기는 놈 때문에
먹지도, 자지도, 아무것도 못하니까요
or do anything because
this guy thinks he owns me.
I know you're scared.
두려운 거 알아
I'm not scared, I'm mad.
두려운 게 아니라
미칠 것 같아요
Why won't someone help me?
왜 아무도
도와주지 않는 거죠?
Should we...
She can handle herself.
우리가...
알아서 하실 거예요
Eric, I know how hard this is,
에릭, 힘든 거 알지만
우린 법을 따라야 해
but we have to follow the law.
You need to stay calm.
침착해야 해
He's not gonna stop.
멈추지 않겠죠
Now I've aggravated him more.
그 녀석을 더 화나게
만들었어요
I don't want to live like this.
이렇게 살 수는 없어요
Nobody gets it.
아무도 몰라요
I get it.
난 알아
Eric, there is nothing you're feeling
에릭, 네가 느끼는 기분
나는 다 알고 있어
that I don't know.
Hey. Believe me, I know.
나는 아니까 믿어
I've been through this,
나도 겪었어
much worse than this,
훨씬 더 심했지
and it will not get the best of you
언젠가는 끝날 테니
네 본모습을 해치지 못할 거야
because it will end.
I'm going to help you.
내가 도와줄게
Eric, if you need anything,
I'm here, OK?
도움이 필요하면
나를 찾아와, 알겠지?
Call anytime.
언제든 전화하고
OK. I've got something.
좋아요, 찾았어요
It's Lori Carter.
로리 카터네요
Larry Myers was stalking both women.
래리 마이어스가
둘 다를 스토킹했어
There he is.
저기 나오는군
Oh, that's creepy.
저건 좀 소름끼치네
Whoa!
워!
There's another person.
한 사람 더 있어
Two stalkers?
두 명이라고요?
Larry had a partner.
파트너가 있었던 거야
Keep searching. Find me a face.
계속 보고
얼굴 찾아내
The second stalker
never appears on camera
두 번째 스토커는
화면에 전혀 안 나와요
in any of the footage.
Did Larry admit to an accomplice?
래리가 공범을 자백했나요?
No. His lawyer shut me down.
아니, 변호사가 막았어
Jack's trying to break his wife.
잭이 부인을
신문하고 있어
You knew he was having an affair.
남편이 바람을 피운 걸
알고 계셨겠죠
Of course I knew.
물론 알았죠
I predicted it.
예상하고 있었어요
Larry isn't special. He's right on point
래리도 다를 바 없이
중년의 위기를 겪었어요
with his midlife crisis.
Started with his 48th birthday.
48번째 생일에
시작됐죠
Suddenly, 50's staring him in the face,
불현듯 50살이
닥쳐오고
and he's thinking about
everything he's not gonna be,
이루지 못한 것이나
원했던 삶, 또 다른 걸 꿈꿨어요
the life he wanted,
the one he got instead.
Started going to the gym.
운동을 시작했고요
The gym is where
he met Kate, right?
케이트가 다녔던
헬스장 말씀이시죠?
I suppose.
그렇겠죠
He started staying out late.
귀가가 늦어지고
I found cocaine in his pants pocket.
바지 주머니에서
코카인을 찾았어요
He said it wasn't his but a friend's,
친구 거라고 하더군요
his new "bro"... His word.
새로운 '절친' 이라나...
This friend have a name?
그 친구 이름은 아세요?
I don't remember a name.
이름은 기억 안나요
Troy Gunn?
'트로이 건'인가요?
No. That doesn't sound right.
그런 이름은
아니었어요
It was more like a stage name.
예명 같은 느낌인데
This guy was a trainer at the gym.
헬스장 트레이너였죠
Kurt wild?
'커트 와일드'요?
Yes, that's it.
네, 맞아요
They were playing a game,
같이 게임을 즐겼어요
feeding each other's
obsession, a midlife crisis,
먹잇감을 거들면서,
중년의 위기에 자극을 찾았죠
looking for a pulse,
and Larry finds it...
Courtesy of a failed actor
in need of an audience.
관객이 필요했던
삼류 배우의 호의로요
Those two women were props
to their own self-obsession.
피해자들은 이들의
소품 같은 존재였어요
Kurt wild's real name
is Buford Posey.
커트 와일드의 본명은
'뷰포드 포지'예요
Good call with the name change.
이름 바꾸길 잘했군
Domestic abuse, two arrests.
가정 폭력으로
두 번 체포됐는데
Beat up his girlfriend
some years back,
몇 년 전 여자친구를
폭행했거든요
anger issues,
online gambling conviction,
'분노 조절 장애'에
온라인 게임 중독
juvenile detention starting at 12.
12살 때부터
소년원에 들락거렸어요
Yes, Kurt murdered Kate Edwards,
커트가 케이트를 죽였고
지금 어디 있는지 모릅니다
and I don't know where he is.
It was supposed to be fun.
재미로 한 짓이고
해를 끼치지도 않았어요
It was harmless, you know?
We each picked a girl to follow.
각각 저는 케이트를,
그는 로리를 대상으로 골랐죠
I picked Kate, he picked Lori.
But you dated Kate.
당신은 케이트와 사귀었지만
커트는 아니었지
He didn't date Lori.
Well, Kurt was more into the watching,
커트는 보는 걸
좋아했어요
but he helped me.
하지만 절 도와서
케이트를 소개해줬고
He introduced me to Kate
and showed me how to flirt with her,
그녀와 어울려 수작을
거는 방법이랑 어떻게...
hit on her, you know, how to...
Have sex with her.
섹스를 할지 알려줬죠
He coached you.
놈이 가르쳤군
Yeah. It was like
a game till she found out
내가 유부남인 걸
알기 전까지는 게임 같았어요
I was married and dumped me,
so Kurt suggested a new game.
그래서 커트가
새 게임을 제안했죠
Why did Kurt want them dead?
놈이 왜 여자들을
죽이려 했지?
Kate didn't want me, and
Lori didn't want Kurt,
둘 다 우리를
원하지 않기 때문에
so he said we should start over.
새로 시작해야
한다고 하더군요
Whole new game, two new picks.
새로운 대상을 찾아서요
Kurt is not at his home or work.
커트가 현재
집이나 헬스장에 없어서
We have an APB out.
지명 수배를 내렸어요
Where's Lori Carter? Is she save?
로리 카터는?
지금 피신해 있나?
She was released from the hospital
퇴원해서 친구 집으로
데려다 주고 있대요
and is being taken to a friend's house.
Police are with her.
경찰이 동행 중이에요
All clear.
이상 없습니다
친구분 댁으로
모셔다 드리겠습니다
Ma'am, we need to get you
to your friend's house.
I'll just be a minute.
잠시만요
I need to pack a few things.
몇 가지만 챙기고요
Uh, if you don't mind.
괜찮으시면
열어 두시죠
I was gonna change, too.
옷도 갈아
입어야 해요
A compromise.
살짝만 열죠
OK.
네
- How the hell did this happen?
- I don't know.
- 어쩌다 이런 일이?
- 모르겠습니다
She was changing.
We left the door open.
문을 열어 둔 채
옷을 갈아입었어요
OK. He's not gonna
kill her, not right away.
좋아, 바로 당장
죽이지는 않을 거예요
- He would have done it already.
- He's spiraling.
- 아니면 진작 저질렀겠죠
- 점점 막가고 있군
He's had a psychotic break,
and he's playing the game.
정신 분열증을 앓고 있고
게임을 하는 중이에요
He didn't return to his house.
놈이 집에
오지 않았답니다
Traffic is doing a video trail.
교통 카메라로
추적해보는 중이고요
- What about work?
- Gym's closed at this hour.
- 직장은?
- 헬스장은 문 닫았어요
That's where he met both
women, where he met Larry.
거기서 두 여자 모두와
래리를 만났어요
All available units urban burn gym
지금 출동 가능한 팀 모두
브레아로 모이라고 해
on LA Brea now.
Unh!
Don't do this, Kurt.
이러지 마요, 커트
Do you remember what you said
to me when I asked you out?
내가 데이트 신청했을 때
당신이 했던 말 기억나?
You said that you were seeing someone.
만나는 사람이
있다고 했지
You lied. You think I didn't know?
거짓말이었어,
내가 모를 줄 알았나?
I know everything about you!
너에 관한 건 다 알아!
We're friends. We're better as friends.
우리는 친구예요,
친구일 때 좋았잖아요
The game is over. It has to stop.
게임은 끝났어
이제 그만해야지
No! No! No, no, no!
안돼! 제발 안돼요!
Aah! Ohh!
Aah! Aah!
Don't worry. You won't be alone.
걱정하지 마
혼자가 아니잖아
We're gonna do it together.
우리 둘이
함께 할 거야
No! No!
Help me! Help me! Help me!
살려 주세요!
제발 살려 줘요!
We got shots fired.
발포 해도 좋다!
Wait. Wait.
잠깐, 잠깐만요
You don't want to do that.
그러고 싶지 않잖아요
Don't move.
움직이지 마
Unh!
Let's go! Stay down!
They're gonna take
you to the hospital now,
병원으로 모셔다
드릴 겁니다
and I'll meet you there.
거기서 뵙죠
You're gonna be OK.
괜찮으실 거예요
I'll see you tomorrow.
내일 봅시다
What, I get nothing?
뭐 없어요?
What is it you want?
원하는 게 뭐예요?
I want you not to hate me.
날 미워하지
않았으면 해요
Can't guarantee that.
그건 장담 못해요
All right. Then I'm just gonna say it.
됐어요,
그럼 그냥 묻죠
Why do you wear sexy things
주목받는 게 싫다면
왜 섹시한 옷을 입어요?
if you don't want men to notice?
For how I feel in them.
입었을 때의
기분을 위해서요
I dress for myself.
나 자신을 위해
입는 거예요
Nice try.
핑계가 좋네요
Well, good night.
그럼, 좋은 밤 보내요
I thought today went well.
일진이 좋은
날이었어요
I know about New York
뉴욕에서의 일 알아요
and the captain's wife.
상관의 부인과
있었던 일도
Deputy chief's wife.
부청장의 아내였소
Oh.
I made a lot of mistakes in New York,
뉴욕에서 많은
실수를 저질렀어요
some things I can't undo.
되돌릴 수 없는 것들요
So you come to L.A. to be a better man?
더 나은 사람이 되고자
LA에 온 건가요?
You do know that most people
are incapable of change?
대부분의 사람들이
변할 수 없다는 거 알죠?
Well, what can I tell you?
내가 뭐라고 하겠어요?
I'm an underdog story.
난 약자일 뿐이지
I apologize if it it clouded
처음 내 반응이 당신을
우울하게 했다면 사과하죠
my initial reaction to you.
Thank you.
고맙소
All right. We're done
here. I'd like to go home.
그럼 다 된 것 같군요,
집에 가야겠어요
One more thing. Pure curiosity.
궁금한 거
한 가지만 더요
How did you come to run tau?
어쩌다 TAU를
굴리게 된 거죠?
Why this division?
왜 이런 부서죠?
Well, I was married.
결혼을 했었어요
Had a husband and a
kid, and he cheated on me
아이도 있었는데
남편이 바람을 피웠죠
with some crazy woman.
웬 미친 여자랑요
She started stalking us,
followed us everywhere.
우리를 스토킹하고
어디든 따라다녔어요
She showed up at my kid's school,
아이의 학교에도
나타났고
she broke into our house,
she boiled the family...
집에도 침입해서
키우던 동물을 삶았는데...
Bunny.
토끼였죠
I saw that movie, too.
그 영화도 봤어요
Come on. It was a little funny.
그래도 웃겼잖아요
Look. Be patient.
기다려봐요
I don't put it out there
in the first 5 minutes.
5분 만에 전부
쏟아 낼 수는 없잖아요
That'd be creepy.
그럼 소름 끼칠 걸요
Good night, Jack.
잘 자요, 잭
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는 거죠?
Walking.
걷고 있지
How'd you find me?
날 어떻게 찾았어요?
It wasn't hard, Perry.
어려운 일 아니야, 페리
What do you want?
원하는 게 뭐예요?
I know what you're doing.
날 겁주려고
이런다는 거 알아요
You're trying to intimidate me.
Unh! What the hell?
아!
왜 이래요?!
What I'm doing, Perry,
is warning you.
지금 나는
경고를 하는 거야
Stay away from Eric.
에릭한테서 떨어져
You can't do that.
이럴 순 없어요
What, this?
뭐, 이런 거?
You're in trouble, lady.
I'm gonna report y...
당신 큰일 난 거야,
내가 신고...
For what?
뭘로?
Aah!
Stalking a stalker? Go for it.
스토커를 스토킹했다고?
한번 해보던가
You think they're gonna believe
a punk-ass little twit like you?
너같이 찌질한 새끼 말을
누가 믿어 줄 거 같아?
I can lie better than you,
and they believe me.
내가 거짓말도 더 잘하고
다들 내 말만 믿겠지
They always do.
늘 그렇거든
I am not under your family's thumb.
너희 집안 손가락에
내가 까딱이나 할 것 같아?
I will come for you.
널 찾아갈 거야
Stay away from Eric.
에릭 눈에 띄지 마
Did you think I wouldn't find you?
당신 못 봤을 줄 알았어?
Hey, Amanda.
안녕, 아만다
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
New job.
새로운 일
Really? You just chose L.A. out of all
그 많은 도시 중에
LA를 골랐다고?
the cities in the world?
I saw you at school today.
오늘 학교에서
당신을 봤어
Stay away from us, Jack.
우리한테서 떨어져, 잭
I moved her to get away from you.
당신한테서 벗어나려고
이사한 거야
You stay away from my son.
내 아들한테서 떨어져
Don't you mean our son?
- 우리 아들 말인가?
- 아내, 내 아들 말이야
No. I mean my son.
He's mine, not yours.
내 아들이지,
당신 아들 아니야
Amanda.
아만다
I mean it, Jack.
진심이야, 잭
You cannot show up here
and ruin my life, not again.
다시 나타나서 내 인생을
망치게 할 순 없어
That's not why I'm here.
그러려고 온 거 아니야
Leave us alone.
우릴 내버려 둬
I want to change my life.
내 삶을 바꾸고 싶어
I do.
진심이야
I don't want to be
the person you remember.
당신이 기억하던 사람으로
살고 싶지 않아
I don't want to be
the man my own son...
내 하나뿐인
아들에게 그런...
I want to change.
달라지고 싶어
Please.
제발
I have a right to see my son.
나도 그 애를
볼 권리가 있어
Stay away from us, Jack.
우리 앞에서 사라져, 잭
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
translated by "S"
기미갤 Sophie